Claws, Wings, and Fangs
Well? Any luck finding Blaion?
It's no use. No matter how hard I look, I can't find them.
And it doesn't help that the footage is so dark at night...
I haven't seen any posts on social media mentioning a suspicious looking fire truck, either.
Phantom Hornet, Sealed.
Soleil...?
I'll be taking her with me.
You...!
Wait!
Don't follow us!
Aah!
F-Fire!!
Are you okay?
(At the time, I was so shocked that I couldn't do anything.)
Soleil had a Metal Breath.
If she's carrying Blaion around sealed in card form, it'll be impossible to find them.
I suppose that's true...
Ugh... Is there any way I can find Soleil again?
Would things get too complicated if we asked the police for help?
We can't use the public safety radio again. My dad really scolded me for that.
Sorry about that...
Come to think of it, you're the daughter of the mayor, Anna.
Yes, I am. Why?
Tell the mayor:
We need to put the entire city of Mowtown under lockdown immediately!
WHAAAAA?!
What do you mean by that, Mega Ambler?
Why a lockdown all of a sudden?
What do you mean, all of a sudden?! After Phantom Hornet was sealed by that kid, they've gone missing!
If they start spreading the Beast Virus indiscriminately, it’ll be the end of us—
and the end of our coexistence with humans, too!
When the infected Metal Cardbots go on a rampage, the only outcome is total annihilation...!
T-That sounds really bad...
Soleil wouldn't do something like spreading the virus.
How can you be so sure?
She fixed Blue Cop! If she were to go around spreading the virus, she wouldn't have helped us out in the first place!
You’re too naive. She's on the Wild Cardbots' side, after all.
She'll put us in danger with all kinds of lies and deception, just like those Wild Cardbots do!
You're overreacting...!
Then why did she steal your chance to seal a Wild Cardbot and run away?! Answer me!
How should I know that?!
Enough! Calm down, both of you!
Now, now, let's think this through one step at a time, guys.
I'm sorry for yelling.
It's... it's okay. I'm sorry, too.
First, I'll tell my colleagues about the Wild Cardbots...
and that another owner of the Metal Breath has appeared.
Good. I'll leave it to you.
Ugh. Lockdown? There's no way we can do that.
I've never seen Mega Ambler so upset...
He's a doctor, after all. He's seen many lives lost to Wild Cardbots.
Please be understanding, even if he acts a little sensitive.
I thought planet Machina was peaceful until its lifespan came to an end...
I guess even a distant planet isn't all that different from Earth.
Huh? Uncle! Wait up!
What? What? Hey, hey! That was in the trash!
I've got an idea... I know how to find Soleil!
You want me to publish an article about a missing person?
A girl named Soleil has gone missing!
We need to find her as soon as possible!
I can't! I don't have the power to do something like that!
Hey, why are you being such a stranger? We're partners who saved the world together!
Not to mention the photos you took in Porcaca played a crucial role in the coexistence of humans and Metal Cardbots!
Please, Mister Hawkins. Our society of coexistence is under threat.
Well... I do owe you guys for everything. And I really do want to help you guys out, but...
Why are you stalling over there, Jim?! Hurry on over there before it gets away!
Y-yes, sir!!
And you. Don't disturb the adults while they're working.
Ehehehe... What's going on, anyway?
An octopus monster appeared at Landfill No. 30!
An octopus?!
We’re here at the bridge construction site at Landfill No. 30.
Reports are pouring in that a giant octopus monster was spotted here this morning, prompting citizens to remain on high alert.
Could this be related to the unidentified Metal Cardbots that caused a commotion recently?
Oh! There! I saw something!
Well? Do you see anything?
Hmmm... Oh!
I got it! But that's not an octopus. That's a tank!
A tank?!
A tank standing alone in a landfill rich in methane gas...
It's only natural to assume that it's a Metal Cardbot that has come to collect energy.
So that Metal Cardbot is a stranger to you guys, right?
Eh?
Aaaahh!!
Jun!
What's going on?! I thought Metal Cardbots were friends with humans now!
I don't think that's a Metal Cardbot, but a...
We have no choice. Let's head to the landfill!
Alright!
You guys get out of here!
Jun!
Incoming!
Hold on tight!
Where are they?
Be careful, Blue Cop.
ROAR!!!
Yahahahaha!
You're a Metal Cardbot, right?
Blue Cop! Reverse! Reverse!!
I'm on it!
Who are you?!
Grrrhahaha! The name is Tigun!
The strongest Wild Cardbot on planet Machina, if I do say so myself! Grrrhahaha!
Of course.
Ugh... another one of those "I'm the strongest!" guys.
Huh? Whatcha' say?!
Planet Machina disappeared a long time ago.
That title doesn’t mean anything here, so wouldn’t it be better for you to find a new identity here on Earth?
And besides, there are plenty of others who are stronger than you, y'hear?!
And there are worse ones, too!
Who are we talking about??
Grrrhahaha! You've got some guts to preach to me like that!
There's no way we can talk him down, can we?
I wasn't even counting on it.
Blue Cop Wild! Set Up!
Roar!
Burst Gun!
Sniff Sniff. Eh?!
You a Wild Cardbot or a Metal Cardbot? Which side are ya on?!
Jun told me... that kind of thing doesn't matter here!
I am Blue Cop! A resident of Earth!
The heck you sayin'?!
Mega Ambler! Phoenix Fire!
Where's Blue Cop?
They're across the bridge, fighting against a tank.
A tank??
Could this be another Wild Cardbot?
A Wild Cardbot?
Here comes Fleta Z... or not.
I have a bad feeling about this.
If you want to live on this planet, you must respect the lifeforms here!
Everyone will accept you if you do that!
I don't care 'bout any of that. A lone beast like me doesn't need a pack!
Impressive...
If you’re willing to respect others, you can stay with us, too!
Don't make me laugh! Who told you I'd want that?!
Now what?!
You gentlemen look like you're having quite a lot of fun. May I join in too?
When did you call your ally?
What?! I don't know this guy!
It's only a natural instinct for us to be drawn to the scent of battle, isn't it?
Blue Cop! Wolf Howl Shot!!
Who the heck is that guy?
He looks just like Sky Gallop.
Shall we have some delightful fun?
Alpha Bolt Cannon!
Blue Cop!
Are you okay?!
A wound like this is nothing...!
Hmmm... Well, isn’t that strange? I imbued my Crimson Lance with the Beast Virus... yet you show no reaction to it at all?
Ah. I can sense the aura of a raging beast lurking behind that kind face.
You're a Wild Cardbot too, right? Why are you doing this?!
Heh heh... All I will say is that my name is Night Griffon!
Well, well, I can't say that your aim is particularly elegant.
May I suggest you distinguish between enemies and allies when aiming?
Grrrha! I don't care 'bout that. I'm just following my instinct to fight!
Blue Cop, let's retreat for now. Things are looking bad.
Roger that, Jun!
There is no way I'll let you gentlemen get away!
Roar! Get back here!
Huh? Oh! It's Blue Cop!
Is that...?!
Everyone get off of the bridge!
Now, time for you to stop running away!
What was that?!
Deep Bite!
CAAAAAAAAW!!! GET IT OOOOOFF!!! OW!! OW!!!
Blegh. This chicken leg has no taste!
Excuse me?!
Cielo! Set Up!
Whoopsie daisy. Watch your head!
Deep Bite! Set Up!
Huh? We have more challengers?
Trident... Submarine!
Roar!!
Well now, looks like he's no ordinary interloper.
Heh. My excitement has worn off. Until next time!
Hah! I'll turn you into a wild fried chicken if you come back!
Deep Bite!
Yo!
Peruru! Cielo!
Good to see ya, Jun.
That was pretty good timing on our part, wasn't it?
All thanks to me.
Blue Cop, it looks like you've lost a little weight since I last saw you.
Ahaha... I went on a diet.
By the way, when did you guys come to Mowtown?
I called them here.
Crest!
Hey... you could've told me first, Crest.
Sorry. I've been too busy looking into a few things.
I need to talk to you with Deep Bite about the Wild Cardbots.
Grr! Dang it, I can't fire my cannon because it's sopping wet!
I'll be back after I fill my belly! Grrrhahaha!
What do you think? Does this help?
Of course it does. I can now create a vaccine, and it's all because of the sample you brought me.
Thank you, Soleil. You're such a good girl.
If you need anything else, just let me know. I'll do anything you ask, mother.